Connor Meehan

Aspiring Creative Technologist

Connor Meehan

(+44) 7516 678618 connorgmeehan23@gmail.com https://cgm.codes https://github.com/connorgmeehan

Skills

- Working collaboratively
- Asking actionable questions
- Inciting constructive criticism
- Problem solving
- Able to quickly learn systems, codebase and practices

Hello, I'm Connor, I'm a second year Computing Design student and linux nerd who loves the intersection between humans and computers and wants to explore all the wonderful ways of facilitating it. I've been building websites since I was 15, and am passionate about effective designs, clean code and learning about as much of both as I can. I'm goal is to design and develop magical experiences for users, participate and help facilitate a fun, open, collaborative work environment, meet people and produce work to be proud of!

Experience

Pacific Magazines / Junior Engineer - Pacific Digital

User focused design

- o User research
- User centric interface design
- Ability to understand how technologies interact with each other, OOP principles
- JS, frontend application development [ES6, React, jQuery Vue.js, webpack, THREE.js, p5.js]
- CSS, BEM + extensible/reusable stylesheets, [LESS, SASS]
- C#, SOLID principles and MVC [ASP.NET MVC, Unity]
- C++,interactive displays and real time applications, [openFrameworks, Arduino, openCV, Open Lighting Architecture]
- Linux, [Raspian, Ubuntu, Manjaro]

August 2018 - Present, Everleigh

Working collaboratively, asking effective questions, implementing features and bug fixes based on ticket requirements, validating my own work, receiving constructive criticism and responding with follow up questions that promote fast, high quality and accurate development on a number of online magazines (Marie Claire, InStyle, BeautyCrew, Who,

Better Homes and Gardens). [JS (ES6, React, Vue), CSS (LESS), C#, SQL].

Amber Tiles / Labourer

December 2016 - August 2018, Seaforth

Working alone or with one other person making orders, self managing, problem solving and solving IT issues.

Tutor Reactive / Computer Science Tutor

September 2016 - April 2017, Gorden

Building a lesson plan and while communicating software development concepts clearly by using relatable examples and

Education

University of Sydney / Bachelor of Design Computing

March 2017- Present, Camperdown

University of Technology Sydney / Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

March 2016 - November 2016, Haymarket

Awards University of Sydney - 2019 Graduation Show - Most Innovative Design (https://www.cgm.codes/works/face-d-tect/)

> University of Sydney - DECO 2200 Interface Design Studio - Best Concept Design 2018 (https://www.cgm.codes/works/koala-n-joey/)